Finding Aid for the Donald A. Glaser Papers, 1943-2013, bulk 1949-2003 GlaserDA
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Series 5 Bubble Chamber (Ann Arbor), 1942-1994; 5
  - Subseries 3 Publications, 1942-1994
    - CERN (European Organization of Nuclear Research), 1956-1957; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_11 (Box B-5.1, Folder 11)
      1958 materials consist mainly of symposium papers by others; 1958 and 1959 materials also include some correspondence
    - CERN (European Organization of Nuclear Research), 1956-1958; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_12 (Box B-5.1, Folder 12)
      1959 materials consist mainly of symposium papers by others; 1958 and 1959 materials also include some correspondence
    - CERN (European Organization of Nuclear Research), 1956-1959; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_13 (Box B-5.1, Folder 13)
      1960 materials consist mainly of symposium papers by others; 1958 and 1959 materials also include some correspondence
    - CERN (European Organization of Nuclear Research), 1956-1959; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_14 (Box B-5.1, Folder 14)
      1961 materials consist mainly of symposium papers by others; 1958 and 1959 materials also include some correspondence
    - CERN (European Organization of Nuclear Research), 1956-1959; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_15 (Box B-5.1, Folder 15)
      1962 materials consist mainly of symposium papers by others; 1958 and 1959 materials also include some correspondence
    - CERN (European Organization of Nuclear Research), 1956-1959; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_16 (Box B-5.1, Folder 16)
      1963 materials consist mainly of symposium papers by others; 1958 and 1959 materials also include some correspondence
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1957; GlaserDA_05_03_02B_18 (Box B-5.2, Folder 18)
    - Bubble Chambers for Nuclear Physics Experiments, report by David C. Rahm, 1956; GlaserDA_05_03_05C_02 (Box C-5.5, Folder 2)
      Summarizes work done between April 1952 - December 1955
    - The University of Michigan bubble chamber program, CERN Symposium, 1956; GlaserDA_05_03_05C_03 (Box C-5.5, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Annual International Conference on High Energy Physics at CERN, GlaserDA_05_03_05C_04 (Box C-5.5, Folder 4)
    - Book on Bubble Chamber, correspondence regarding, 1958-1960; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_04 (Box B-5.1, Folder 4)
    - Bubble Chamber publications by Glaser, 1953; 1958; 1960; 1994; GlaserDA_05_03_05C_05; Letter, photocopies, reprints, drafts (Box C-5.5, Folder 5)
    - Charge Independence and Hyperons (manuscripts and correspondence), 1957; GlaserDA_05_03_01B_17 (Box B-5.1, Folder 17)
    - Handbuch der Physik, 1957-1967; GlaserDA_05_03_02B_25 (Box B-5.2, Folder 25)
    - Handbuch der Physik, 1957-1967; GlaserDA_05_03_02B_26 (Box B-5.2, Folder 26)
    - Handbuch der Physik, 1957-1967; GlaserDA_05_03_02B_27 (Box B-5.2, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 4 Conferences and talks, 1954-1993
    - Lecture for Bubble Chamber colloquium, 1954; GlaserDA_05_04_03B_08 (Box B-5.3, Folder 8)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_14 (Box B-5.4, Folder 14)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_15 (Box B-5.4, Folder 15)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_16 (Box B-5.4, Folder 16)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_17 (Box B-5.4, Folder 17)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_20 (Box B-5.4, Folder 20)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_21 (Box B-5.4, Folder 21)
    - Rochester Conference, 1954-1960; GlaserDA_05_04_04B_22 (Box B-5.4, Folder 22)
    - Hawaii, 1959; GlaserDA_05_04_02B_28 (Box B-5.2, Folder 28)
    - Moscow, 1959; GlaserDA_05_04_03B_10 (Box B-5.3, Folder 10)
    - Moscow, 1959; GlaserDA_05_04_03B_11 (Box B-5.3, Folder 11)
    - Moscow, 1959; GlaserDA_05_04_03B_05oversize (Box B-5.3, Folder 5oversize)
    - Conference on the Bubble Chamber - Correspondence, 1991 April - 1993 July; GlaserDA_05_04_05C_06 (Box C-5.5, Folder 6)
    - Conference on the Bubble Chamber - Glaser's talk, Invention of the Bubble Chamber and Subsequent Events, 1993 July; GlaserDA_05_04_05C_07 (Box C-5.5, Folder 7)
    - Conference on the Bubble Chamber - Glaser's After Dinner Speech, 1993 July; GlaserDA_05_04_05C_08 (Box C-5.5, Folder 8)
    - Conference on the Bubble Chamber - Poster, 1993 July; GlaserDA_05_04_05C_09 (Box C-5.5, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 5 Miscellaneous material, 1953-1983
    - Bubble Chamber photos, undated; GlaserDA_05_05_05C_10 (Box C-5.5, Folder 10)
    - Stereo systems, 1953; GlaserDA_05_05_05B_03 (Box B-5.5, Folder 3)
    - Press and publicity (mostly regarding Bubble Chamber), 1955-1965; GlaserDA_05_05_03B_22 (Box B-5.3, Folder 22)
    - Press and publicity (mostly regarding Bubble Chamber), 1955-1965; GlaserDA_05_05_03B_23 (Box B-5.3, Folder 23)
    - Press and publicity (mostly regarding Bubble Chamber), 1955-1965; GlaserDA_05_05_03B_24 (Box B-5.3, Folder 24)
    - Press and publicity (mostly regarding Bubble Chamber), 1955-1965; GlaserDA_05_05_03B_25 (Box B-5.3, Folder 25)
    - Press and publicity (mostly regarding Bubble Chamber), 1955-1965 (Box B-5.3, Folder 26)
    - Press and publicity (mostly regarding Bubble Chamber), 1955-1965; GlaserDA_05_05_03B_06oversize (Box B-5.3, Folder 6oversize)
    - Bubble Chamber, Geneva Exhibit, 1957-1959; GlaserDA_05_05_01B_08 (Box B-5.1, Folder 8)
      Includes Brussels World Fair papers
    - "The Birth of the Bubble Chamber - A Moralistic Drinking Song" by Arthur Roberts, 1958 November 1; GlaserDA_05_05_05C_11 (Box C-5.5, Folder 11)
    - Photos from Russian meeting - Kiev, 1959; GlaserDA_05_05_05C_12 (Box C-5.5, Folder 12)
    - Possible Method for Separation of Particles in a Mixed Particle Beam (Research Note No.1, 1960; GlaserDA_05_05_06B_11 (Box B-5.6, Folder 11)
    - Bubble Chamber related correspondence, 1963; 1979; 1982; 1983; GlaserDA_05_05_05C_13 (Box C-5.5, Folder 13)
      Includes letter regarding patent claim
    - Bubble Chamber correspondence, 1982-1983; GlaserDA_05_05_11B_02 (Box B-5.11, Folder 2)
- Series 6 Molecular Biology, 1958-2005; 6
  Biographical / Historical
  Donald Glaser's biology work included research in microbiology and theoretical biology and lead to the designs of the Cyclops, an automatic cell inoculator, and well as the Dumbwaiter, an automated system for the growth and analysis of large numbers of bacterial colonies.
  - Subseries 1 Notes, lectures, and talks, 1963-1993
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars I, undated; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_01 (Box C-6.1, Folder 1)
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars II, 1963 February - December; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_02 (Box C-6.1, Folder 2)
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars III, 1964 January - November; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_03 (Box C-6.1, Folder 3)
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars IV, 1965 January - November; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_04 (Box C-6.1, Folder 4)
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars V, 1966 January - 1967 December; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_05 (Box C-6.1, Folder 5)
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars VI, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_06 (Box C-6.1, Folder 6)
    - Molecular Biology notes, lectures, and seminars VII, 1978-1981; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_07 (Box C-6.1, Folder 7)
    - Course: Molecular Biology 270 (Control of macromolecular synthesis in bacteria), 1966; GlaserDA_06_01_06B_1a (Box B-6.6, Folder 1a)
    - Lectures given by Donald Glaser, 1968-1972; GlaserDA_06_01_06B_09 (Box B-6.6, Folder 9)
    - Theoretical Biology notes, lectures, and seminars I, 1967-1977; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_08 (Box C-6.1, Folder 8)
    - Theoretical Biology notes, lectures, and seminars II, 1980-1981; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_09 (Box C-6.1, Folder 9)
    - Notes from the Institut de la Vie Conference, Versailles, 1969 July 9; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_10 (Box C-6.1, Folder 10)
    - Institute de la Vie, 1975-1982; GlaserDA_06_01_12B_29 (Box B-6.12, Folder 29)
    - Institute de la Vie, 1975-1982; GlaserDA_06_01_12B_30 (Box B-6.12, Folder 30)
    - Diffusion notes, ca. 1974-1981; GlaserDA_06_01_01C_11 (Box C-6.1, Folder 11)
    - Black Lightning lecture notes, 1993; GlaserDA_06_01_10B_47 (Box B-6.10, Folder 47)
  - Subseries 2 Publications by others, 1961-1990
    - Baer, R.M., 1966 February; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_01 (Box C-6.2, Folder 1)
      Technical report, correspondence
    - Beischer, Dietrich E., 1962-1964; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_02 (Box C-6.2, Folder 2)
      Reprints, correspondence
    - Bischof, Norbert, 1970; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_03 (Box C-6.2, Folder 3)
      Draft
    - Burger, Richard M., 1971; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_04 (Box C-6.2, Folder 4)
      Reprints
    - Cohen, Joel E., 1979; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_05 (Box C-6.2, Folder 5)
      Draft (photocopy), author note
    - Crick, F.H.C., 1967; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_06 (Box C-6.2, Folder 6)
      Photocopy, correspondence from 1972
    - Crutchfield, J.P & Jeffries, C.D., 1986-1990; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_07 (Box C-6.2, Folder 7)
      National Science Foundation project summary
    - Delbruck, Max, 1962; 1963; 1969; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_08 (Box C-6.2, Folder 8)
      Reprints and photocopy, author notes
    - V. Fernandez-Moran, 1964-1983; GlaserDA_06_02_12B_16 (Box B-6.12, Folder 16)
    - Gardner, Martin, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_09 (Box C-6.2, Folder 9)
      Photocopies, Glaser notes from 1979
    - Glass, Bentley, 1963; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_10 (Box C-6.2, Folder 10)
      Reprint, author note, Glaser notes
    - Henning, Ulf, 1971; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_11 (Box C-6.2, Folder 11)
      Draft, correspondence
    - Hillis, W. Daniel, 1984; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_12 (Box C-6.2, Folder 12)
      Reprint (photocopy)
    - Kendall, M.G., undated; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_13 (Box C-6.2, Folder 13)
      Book chapter draft
    - Kung, Ching-kai, undated; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_14 (Box C-6.2, Folder 14)
      Article (photocopy), note from author's son from 1979
    - Landauer, Rolf, 1976; 1979; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_15 (Box C-6.2, Folder 15)
      Reprint, draft, correspondence
    - Levins, Richard, ca. 1973; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_16 (Box C-6.2, Folder 16)
      Draft (photocopy)
    - Mandelbrot, Benoit, 1969; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_17 (Box C-6.2, Folder 17)
      Draft, correspondence, photograph, notes by Glaser
    - Mayr, Ernst, 1961; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_18 (Box C-6.2, Folder 18)
      Reprint (photocopy), notes by Glaser
    - Pattee, H.H., 1969; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_19 (Box C-6.2, Folder 19)
    - Pollack, R., Pfeiffer, S., 1971; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_20 (Box C-6.2, Folder 20)
      Course manual
    - Ryan, Francis J., ca. 1963; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_21 (Box C-6.2, Folder 21)
      Photocopy not dated, Glaser notes from 1969
    - Schleif, Robert, 1967-1968; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_22 (Box C-6.2, Folder 22)
    - Scotti, Paul D., 1969; 1971; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_23 (Box C-6.2, Folder 23)
    - Silver, Simon, 1967; 1968; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_24 (Box C-6.2, Folder 24)
    - Spetner, L.M., 1964; 1966; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_25 (Box C-6.2, Folder 25)
      Articles (photocopies), notes by Glaser
    - Wolfram, Stephen, 1983; GlaserDA_06_02_02C_26 (Box C-6.2, Folder 26)
      Glaser notes from 1985
  - Subseries 3 Publications by Glaser, 1964-1977
    - Drafts, 1964-1972; GlaserDA_06_03_03C_01 (Box C-6.3, Folder 1)
    - Published work, 1966-1977; GlaserDA_06_03_03C_02 (Box C-6.3, Folder 2)
      Reprints, book chapter photocopies
  - Subseries 4 Scientific and technical documents, 1963-1985
    - Patent claims, 1963; GlaserDA_06_04_03C_03 (Box C-6.3, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence
    - Research proposals, 1964; 1977; GlaserDA_06_04_03C_04 (Box C-6.3, Folder 4)
    - Procedural reports, 1964; 1965; GlaserDA_06_04_03C_05 (Box C-6.3, Folder 5)
    - Grant FR-3, reports regarding, 1964-1965; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_03 (Box B-6.6, Folder 3)
    - Grant FR-3, reports regarding, 1964-1965; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_04 (Box B-6.6, Folder 4)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_12 (Box B-6.6, Folder 12)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_13 (Box B-6.6, Folder 13)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_14 (Box B-6.6, Folder 14)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_17 (Box B-6.6, Folder 17)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_18 (Box B-6.6, Folder 18)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_19 (Box B-6.6, Folder 19)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_20 (Box B-6.6, Folder 20)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_21 (Box B-6.6, Folder 21)
    - Teknekron, assorted files, 1969-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_22 (Box B-6.6, Folder 22)
    - Grants: NIH No. 5 R01 GM22021, 1975-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_05 (Box B-6.6, Folder 5)
    - Grants: NIH No. RR00961, 1975-1980; GlaserDA_06_04_06B_06 (Box B-6.6, Folder 6)
    - Cancer research, 1980-1981; GlaserDA_06_04_11B_05 (Box B-6.11, Folder 5)
    - FIBER (Fund for Integrative Biomedical Research), 1981; GlaserDA_06_04_12B_17 (Box B-6.12, Folder 17)
    - International Council for Scientific Development, 1981; GlaserDA_06_04_13B_02 (Box B-6.13, Folder 2)
    - Grants: new proposals, 1981-1982; GlaserDA_06_04_12B_26 (Box B-6.12, Folder 26)
    - Grant proposal: biomedical research, 1982-1983; GlaserDA_06_04_12B_24 (Box B-6.12, Folder 24)
    - Henry Ehrlich, 1984-1985; GlaserDA_06_04_12B_10 (Box B-6.12, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 5 Biotechnology, 1958-2005
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_13 (Box B-6.5, Folder 13)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_14 (Box B-6.5, Folder 14)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_15 (Box B-6.5, Folder 15)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_16 (Box B-6.5, Folder 16)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_17 (Box B-6.5, Folder 17)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_18 (Box B-6.5, Folder 18)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_19 (Box B-6.5, Folder 19)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_20 (Box B-6.5, Folder 20)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_21 (Box B-6.5, Folder 21)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, assorted files, 1958-1972; GlaserDA_06_05_05B_22 (Box B-6.5, Folder 22)
    - Berkeley Scientific Laboratories, 1965-1967; GlaserDA_06_05_03C_06 (Box C-6.3, Folder 6)
    - Cetus Corporation, 1973-2005; GlaserDA_06_05_03C_07 (Box C-6.3, Folder 7)
    - Computer--Cetus, 1979-1981; GlaserDA_06_05_11B_12 (Box B-6.11, Folder 12)
    - Cetus Corporation, 1981-1982; GlaserDA_06_05_11B_06 (Box B-6.11, Folder 6)
    - Offprint of Glaser's chapter in New technologies and the future of food and nutrition proceedings (Biotechnology and industry), 1989-1991; GlaserDA_06_05_15B_18 (Box B-6.15, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 6 Miscellaneous material, 1965-1996
    - Correspondence, 1965-1967; GlaserDA_06_06_03C_08 (Box C-6.3, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1980; GlaserDA_06_06_06B_10 (Box B-6.6, Folder 10)
    - Molecular biology lab photos and portraits, ca. 1965-1980; GlaserDA_06_06_03C_09 (Box C-6.3, Folder 9)
      Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory photographs
    - IBM, 1966-1967; GlaserDA_06_06_06B_07 (Box B-6.6, Folder 7)
    - IBM, 1966-1967; GlaserDA_06_06_06B_08 (Box B-6.6, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Chronicle article regarding loss of funding, 1980 January 23; GlaserDA_06_06_03C_10 (Box C-6.3, Folder 10)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute (SERI), 1980-1981; GlaserDA_06_06_13B_35 (Box B-6.13, Folder 35)
    - Molecular Biology: Finance Committee, 1981; GlaserDA_06_06_13B_16 (Box B-6.13, Folder 16)
    - Molecular Biology, 1981-1984; GlaserDA_06_06_13B_14 (Box B-6.13, Folder 14)
    - Biomagnetism, 1982 (Box B-6.10, Folder 44)
    - Biology, 1982-1984; GlaserDA_06_06_10B_46 (Box B-6.10, Folder 46)
    - David Busch, 1987-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_11B_03 (Box B-6.11, Folder 3)
    - David Busch, 1987-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_11B_04 (Box B-6.11, Folder 4)
    - Lang, Serge, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_14B_40 (Box B-6.14, Folder 40)
    - Lang, Serge, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_14B_41 (Box B-6.14, Folder 41)
    - Lang, Serge, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_15B_01 (Box B-6.15, Folder 1)
    - Lang, Serge, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_15B_02 (Box B-6.15, Folder 2)
    - Lang, Serge, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_15B_03 (Box B-6.15, Folder 3)
    - Lang, Serge, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_06_15B_04 (Box B-6.15, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 7 Oversize material, undated
    - Glaser group cartoon, undated; GlaserDA_06_07_04C_01; 9.25"x11.75" framed, hand drawn image (Box C-6.4, Folder 1)
    - UC Berkeley Molecular Biology and Virus Laboratory Dumbwaiter drawing, undated; GlaserDA_06_07_04C_02; 11"x17" printed drawing (Box C-6.4, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 8 UC Berkeley Virus Lab and departmental material, 1961-1996
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Research and maps materials, 1961-1967; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_16 (Box B-6.7, Folder 16)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962-1980; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_15 (Box B-6.7, Folder 15)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: equipment, 1964; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_18 (Box B-6.7, Folder 18)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: green screen, 1964; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_14 (Box B-6.7, Folder 14)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Meeting minutes, Programmers and Engineers, 1964-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_01 (Box B-6.7, Folder 1)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Meeting minutes, Programmers and Engineers, 1964-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_02 (Box B-6.7, Folder 2)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Meeting minutes, Programmers and Engineers, 1964-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_03 (Box B-6.7, Folder 3)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Meeting minutes, Programmers and Engineers, 1964-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_04 (Box B-6.7, Folder 4)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_30 (Box B-6.9, Folder 30)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_31 (Box B-6.9, Folder 31)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_32 (Box B-6.9, Folder 32)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_33 (Box B-6.9, Folder 33)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_01 (Box B-6.10, Folder 1)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_02 (Box B-6.10, Folder 2)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_03 (Box B-6.10, Folder 3)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Phil Spielman lab journal, 1968-1973; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_04 (Box B-6.10, Folder 4)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Leif Hansen's reports, 1968-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_03 (Box B-6.8, Folder 3)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Leif Hansen's reports, 1968-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_04 (Box B-6.8, Folder 4)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Leif Hansen's reports, 1968-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_05 (Box B-6.8, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Auxilliary system, 1969; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_12 (Box B-6.7, Folder 12)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: M. Hane's reports, 1969-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_01 (Box B-6.8, Folder 1)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: progress and annual reports, 1970; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_20 (Box B-6.7, Folder 20)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_01 (Box B-6.9, Folder 1)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_02 (Box B-6.9, Folder 2)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_03 (Box B-6.9, Folder 3)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_04 (Box B-6.9, Folder 4)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_05 (Box B-6.9, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_06 (Box B-6.9, Folder 6)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_07 (Box B-6.9, Folder 7)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_08 (Box B-6.9, Folder 8)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_09 (Box B-6.9, Folder 9)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_10 (Box B-6.9, Folder 10)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_11 (Box B-6.9, Folder 11)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_12 (Box B-6.9, Folder 12)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_13 (Box B-6.9, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_14 (Box B-6.9, Folder 14)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_15 (Box B-6.9, Folder 15)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_16 (Box B-6.9, Folder 16)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_17 (Box B-6.9, Folder 17)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_18 (Box B-6.9, Folder 18)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_19 (Box B-6.9, Folder 19)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_20 (Box B-6.9, Folder 20)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_21 (Box B-6.9, Folder 21)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_22 (Box B-6.9, Folder 22)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_23 (Box B-6.9, Folder 23)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_24 (Box B-6.9, Folder 24)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_25 (Box B-6.9, Folder 25)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_26 (Box B-6.9, Folder 26)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_27 (Box B-6.9, Folder 27)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_28 (Box B-6.9, Folder 28)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Potassium, Magnesium, Sodium lab experiment files, 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_09B_29 (Box B-6.9, Folder 29)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_05 (Box B-6.10, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_06 (Box B-6.10, Folder 6)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_07 (Box B-6.10, Folder 7)